I'm Lino Fukuyama aka Lino Maru, the Candy Tune Light Blue!
I'm so serious to the point of disgust.
I feel so guilty about breaking the rules, even if it's just a little bit.
I'm very strict with myself.
I tend to be too strict when I should be more lenient.
I've been told by myself and others that I'm stoic, but when it comes to dieting, I'm really good at achieving something visible in a number, like 3 for everyone.
I am often told that I am more serious than I thought,
I thought I was the type of person who wanted diversity and took good care of people,
But as we got to know each other better
But as we've gotten to know each other better, I've been told that I'm more baby-like than I thought.
I used to watch the Olympics pretty much every time.
I have a habit of watching the Olympics every time they are on TV.
And when I saw the women's basketball team in action, I realized how interesting the sport of basketball is.
I first learned how interesting the sport of basketball was there.
I had never played basketball before, so in my mind, athletes are people who live in a very different world,
I had an image of athletes as stoic, geniuses, and people with great talent who make the most of their talents,
But when I read in a book that the amount of exercise an idol uses is more than that of an athlete during the season, I became interested in athletes,
I became interested in athletes,
My mother invited me to a basketball game at that time,
Seeing them fight so seriously in front of me gave me a lot of power, and that's when I fell in love with them. I was really interested in girls who were really serious,
I think that girls have to show their true, bare instincts,
I think it is rare to see a girl really trying her hardest.
I think it is a pleasure to see that up close and personal,
I think it is the joy of sports sensitivity to be able to see it up close,
I prefer watching them live to watching them on TV, where you can only see them from afar,
I prefer to watch live than on TV, where you can only see it from afar.
I prefer to watch live than on TV, where you can only see it from afar, and I go to see it every week.
The most important thing is that I enjoy doing it,
I think the most enjoyable thing about dance is that you can communicate something just by watching it, because you don't need language to dance.
I am a bit of a nerd for idol choreographers,
I like his choreography.
So I pay a lot of attention to understanding the choreography.
I understand the choreographer's choreography and swallow it by myself.
I understand the choreographer's choreography, swallow it, and share it with the members, saying, "This is the meaning of this part.
I'm a little embarrassed to say that this is one of the keywords I hold up.
I think that idols should be idols before they are girls.
I think there are many idols who say "I'm just a girl,
But I want to be an idol in front of everyone,
I want to be an idol in front of everyone, so I always think about entertaining the people in front of me first and foremost, before my own feelings.
I'm excited.
When I think about what people tweet when they start something like this, I think people tend to say, "I'm anxious, but I'm going to do my best.
But I'm not anxious at the moment.
I'm not anxious right now, so I just want to enjoy it.
I think we can be whatever we want to be, since we don't know what we want yet.
I hope we can establish our own style.
I want my existence to be a source of motivation and hope for someone's life.
I lived in America when I was little.
I lived in America when I was little, and I really didn't understand English at that time.
I cried a lot every day.
That's when I met a Japanese idol.
That was really the hope of life for me.
I wanted to be like them.
Through dance, which I love
I thought 10 years ago that I would like to become someone who can give someone a smile and cheer them up, and that's how I came to be an idol.
I still want to make people around the world smile, and I myself have received energy from the other side of the world, so I want to make more and more people around the world smile and cheer up.
I want to bring smiles and energy to more and more people around the world.
Candy Tune is a place that makes me happy.